{
    "id": "c6d431c882c84f54b59be929fe239495",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am waiting …………………….. a call from my brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "532acf62ee114417a7eedfeba18c98ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t agree ………………………… your opinion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "921a8b872ce049098a3303bce25b045a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can never count ……………………… selfish people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cf592f4880cc4209be108d4e225c39f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He belongs ………………………. a martial clan.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b358fb8b905840288c05fc8542ad5fb0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is full ……………………… ambition.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7f14d78326974e15b72665353c412869"
        },
        {
            "question": "A lot of people die …………………………. malaria.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "676bb4387290409b89a6f585e1ec43dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "They took him ………………………… the doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "172d5b7b194e4d139e87fc0439785c66"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have made dinner ………………………….. you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a0eca10e9a4849c3be0c07c1cf349a55"
        },
        {
            "question": "She got married ………………………….. her childhood friend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0c3903c63a0b4e97b9b9cb6ccb2ff0a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you agree …………………………. the argument that smoking should be banned in public places?",
            "description": "We agree with a view, opinion, argument or policy. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "81cb79206a814531b0e9237b29d65caa"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is quite good ………………………….. fooling people.",
            "description": "We say good or bad at.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d68a3471985246038ce6bb3ee9feff77"
        },
        {
            "question": "Everyone praised the girl ……………………….. her honesty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "65ede8da6b4d42a0adba922ba9128986"
        }
    ]
}